现在我们的应用在显示真实的数据  我们应该
Now that our app is showing real data, we should take
抓取一张应用的截屏  这样我们就可以记住做到这一步的时候
a screenshot of our app, so we can remember what it was
应用是什么样的  我个人在开发应用
like when we made it this far. I personally like doing this
的过程中很喜欢这样做  因为最后我在回顾的时候
throughout the process of building an app, because then I can look
可以看到它是如何不断进步的  我来给大家演示
back, and see how it evolved. I'm going to show you one
一种给设备截屏的方法  打开
way that you can take a screenshot of your device. Open up
Android设备监控器并点击这里的设备  然后
Android Device Monitor and then click on the device here. Then, click
点击这个照相机的标志进行截屏  当截好的屏幕图片弹出
on this camera icon, to do a screen capture. When it pops
的时候  你可以点击保存  这样就完成了截屏
up, you can hit Save, and then you're done.
在某些真实设备上  其实是有物理按键让你
On certain physical devices, there are actually hardware keys that
进行截屏操作的  比如
allow you to grab a screenshot. For example, on the
在Nexus 5上  你可以同时长按音量下键
Nexus 5, you can long press on the volume down
和电源键  这样就可以
and the power key, at the same time. That takes
截屏了  图片会被保存到相册中
a screenshot. It gets saved to the Photos app and
然后你就可以分享给任何你想分享的人了
then you can share it out to anyone you want.
你可以给他们展示你正在开发的应用有多么棒
You can show them what an awesome app you're building.